

## **Summary**

Experienced Graphic Designer and Web Developer with 5 years experience in professional print production settings and working with in-house design teams, artists, and manufacturers. Over 10 years experience working with the Adobe Creative Suite producing graphics and assets for businesses and individuals. Innovative thinker who has re-shaped work spaces improving quality of work and life.

#### Education

Full Stack Web and Mobile Development, Nucamp Coding BootcampBFA Printmaking, Maryland Institute College of Art, Baltimore MD

### **Professional Experience**

# 2019 - 21 Graphic Designer/Production Artist, Denial Print Company, Folsom PA

- •Developed graphic art and designs for clients for the purpose of garment and merchandise printing.
- •Automated workflow to increase accuracy, quality, and efficiency of the in-house production workflow.
- •Revised the company's web presence by building web assets, social media templates, and advertisements.
- •Generated online forms to improve the customer's experience and improve the internal quality of life for the sales department.

Tasks: Prepress, Finishing, Qvvuality Control, File Management, Product Finishing, Large Format Printing.

## 2018 Intern, Applied Image LLC, Freehold NJ

- •Produced large format and environmental graphics for clients including the National Aquarium in Baltimore.
- •Produced artwork for murals under the supervision of the graphic design team.
- •Up-kept studio quality and performed general maintenance on printers and plotters Tasks: Pre-press, Finishing, Printing, Plotting, Weeding, Laminating, Studio Maintenance.

## 2016 - 18 Printer Technician, MICA, Baltimore MD

- •Managed the digital printing studio at the Printmaking Department facilities.
- •Established the foundation of the department's risograph press by producing color charts and running workshops for students.
- •Educated students on fine art digital printing, screen printing, and best studio practices.
- •Acted as a consultant in digital printing processes for visiting artists and the student body.

  Tasks: Pre-press, Consultant, Educator, Hosted regularly scheduled workshops and office hours.

## 2014 - 18 Studio Assistant, Quentin Mosely, Jimmy Joe Roche, Baltimore MD

- •Designed and created custom 16mm film hardware for the short film Skin of Man.
- •Printed cover art, inserts, and advertisement materials for the music label Ultra Violet Light.
- •Assisted in constructing a large public installation for the first annual Light City Baltimore.

Skills	Languages & Software	Skills
	Adobe Suite (Illustrator, Photoshop, After Effects,	Project Management, Customer Service, A/V
	Indesign, Premiere, Audition, Medium)	Production, Screen Printing, Large Format
	Spark AR, Rhinoceros, HTML, CSS/SCSS/Sass,	Printing
	Javascript, React, Redux	•